[
  {
    "question": "Which of the following artworks was created FIRST?",
    "a": "Cho-looke the Yosemite Fall",
    "b": "Rhine Water Purification Plant",
    "c": "In Advance of a Broken Arm",
    "d": "Sun Tunnels",
    "e": "Spiral Jetty",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which environmental term dates from 1935?",
    "a": "ecosystem",
    "b": "biodiversity",
    "c": "greenhouse gas",
    "d": "sustainability",
    "e": "carbon footprint",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rebecca Belmore was born in the same year as the",
    "a": "founding of the World Wildlife Fund",
    "b": "designation of Yellowstone as the first national park",
    "c": "creation of the Environmental Protection Agency",
    "d": "establishment of the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge",
    "e": "ratification of the Clean Air Act",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which text did Jack Burnham publish in 1968?",
    "a": "“Design with Nature”",
    "b": "“Systems Esthetics”",
    "c": "“The Wilderness Act”",
    "d": "“Desert Solitaire”",
    "e": "“Silent Spring”",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did a catastrophic oil spill occur in 1969?",
    "a": "Miami, Florida",
    "b": "Anchorage, Alaska",
    "c": "New Orleans, Louisiana",
    "d": "Galveston, Texas",
    "e": "Santa Barbara, California",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guillermo Calzadilla was born shortly after",
    "a": "Nancy Holt created Sun Tunnels",
    "b": "Robert Smithson created Spiral Jetty",
    "c": "Ana Mendieta created Untitled: Silueta Series",
    "d": "Jennifer Allora was born",
    "e": "Alma Woodsey Thomas died",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Harrisons created Shrimp Farm before",
    "a": "the Watts Rebellion took place in Los Angeles",
    "b": "the Church Rock uranium mill breached its dam",
    "c": "Duchamp created In Advance of a Broken Arm",
    "d": "Pierre Huyghe was born",
    "e": "the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge was established",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following artworks took the LONGEST to create?",
    "a": "Battle for the Woodlands",
    "b": "Flint is Family",
    "c": "Spiral Jetty",
    "d": "Untilled",
    "e": "Sun Tunnels",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many years did Ana Mendieta spend on the 'Silueta' series?",
    "a": "8",
    "b": "3",
    "c": "7",
    "d": "10",
    "e": "5",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many years after the Church Rock uranium spill did Will Wilson create Church Rock Spill Evaporation Ponds?",
    "a": "70",
    "b": "50",
    "c": "40",
    "d": "30",
    "e": "60",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two artworks were created in the same year?",
    "a": "Wheatfield—A Confrontation and Sun Tunnels",
    "b": "Untilled and Battle for the Woodlands",
    "c": "Land Mark (Foot Prints) and Caribou Migration I",
    "d": "Rhine Water Purification Plant and Untitled: Silueta Series",
    "e": "The Fourth World and Flint is Family",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following artworks were created in the 2010s EXCEPT",
    "a": "The Fourth World",
    "b": "Marat (Sebastião), Pictures of Garbage",
    "c": "Battle for the Woodlands",
    "d": "Untilled",
    "e": "Unmoored",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ana Mendieta died shortly after",
    "a": "Flint, Michigan, changed its water source to the Flint River",
    "b": "Vik Muniz created Marat (Sebastião), Pictures of Garbage",
    "c": "Rebecca Belmore created Ayum-ee-aawach Oomama-mowan: Speaking to Their Mother",
    "d": "the US reinstated protections against drilling in the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge",
    "e": "Agnes Denes created Wheatfield—A Confrontation",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Noah Purifoy could NOT have ever learned about the",
    "a": "Church Rock Uranium Spill",
    "b": "Kanesatake Resistance",
    "c": "Watts Rebellion",
    "d": "Flint Water Crisis",
    "e": "Ipperwash Crisis",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following artworks was created LAST?",
    "a": "Church Rock Spill Evaporation Ponds",
    "b": "Offshore Drilling",
    "c": "Wheatfield—A Confrontation",
    "d": "Caribou Migration I",
    "e": "The Fourth World",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  }
]